[Hotel PAL]
Haru, I...
I'm sorry.
I got ahead of myself.
A weird switch flipped in me.
I can't believe I was so giddy about this.
I'm so sorry I led you on.
Please, don't apologize.
I was waiting for that switch to flip.
You only ever saw me as a coworker.
But to me, you were special.
And then you suddenly got married.
Truthfully, part of me always hoped
a day like this would come.
I'm sorry I took advantage
of your momentary hesitation.
You're a creator I respect, Shibuya.
That hasn't ever changed.
Good luck writing those extra 100 pages.
Is now really the time?
Just got back to my hotel.
Our boys' trip is going great.
Hope you had a good day.
What am I doing?
[Episode 11]
You almost had sex with a coworker?
You, Haru?
The late blooming stalker?
Don't poke at my dark past.
I'm just impressed by the evolution.
- Have I really "evolved"?
- Huh?
I went from fussy-stalker, to wife.
From pent up, to relieved.
And as a result, I got way ahead of myself.
When you put it that way,
it sounds more like you regressed.
Before, you were more earnest about Ouji.
You think so, too?
It's tough, isn't it?
Even when you're honest with yourself,
you don't know what's right.
You lose sight of what's important.
And ultimately, you spiral all over again.
Ugh.
- I wanna disappear.
- Huh?
I couldn't hold myself back.
I said something super clingy to Naoki.
You did?
I thought I'd never understand people
who were swayed by love.
But at this rate, he'll only hate me.
I'm scared. I don't want him to hate me.
It's like...
It's like I'm losing myself.
It hurts.
Of course you're scared.
I was, too.
I didn't want Ouji to hate me.
So I thought I'd keep everything to myself.
But that was difficult.
Eventually, I exploded.
Maybe that's why I regressed at all.
It did make me feel a bit better, though.
Except, now I'm more confused.
Maybe I'm not as earnest anymore.
And I don't exactly know
what I want in my future, but...
I'm chugging this.
I...
I'm going to go confess, right now.
- Huh?
- What?
It's something I need to do,
so I don't lose myself.
I want his body and heart to be all mine.
Watching this is even more nerve-wracking...
He's here.
Akina!
Long time no see. Thanks for calling me.
No, thank you for coming on short notice.
It's no problem.
I'm sorry for the other night.
I know it must've been awkward.
I got so depressed on you.
You must think I'm crazy, right?
With the amount of intimacy
we've experienced,
it's only natural to want more.
But...
It's against the business contract, right?
Sorry.
Naoki.
I'm sure you can already tell, but...
I...
I love you.
I've never loved another person before.
I've never felt so obsessed.
I've never felt so jealous.
It all makes me hate myself.
But...
Right now...
I'm just glad you're here.
Thank you.
I also love you, Akina.
But I have to be honest.
I'm polyamorous.
Polyamorous?
I've always felt obliged to reply
to anyone who's showed me love.
No matter how many partners I may have.
It's hurt many people I've come to know.
I apologize for causing you such pain.
I love you.
It doesn't hurt.
Drinking the night away
while I put our daughter to bed, huh?
Toshiki.
We need to talk.
What's up?
I was reminiscing.
About what?
About when we first met.
Even though our feelings were mutual,
you were always especially considerate of me.
Because sex chose to give me another chance,
I felt like I had to take that opportunity
while I could.
Really?
Shota.
You taught me to treasure myself.
Thank you.
You've changed me for the better, too.
I'm counting on you for my next shoot, okay?
Don't worry, I'll do my job.
But...
This has to end.
"Just as life has no happy ending,"
"the explorations of love and sex
do not last forever."
What do you think?
It's as though you're denouncing
the sexual adventure
your protagonist had in the main story.
That wasn't my intent.
She's just faced with reality.
Reality?
After witnessing the outcome
of her friends' journeys,
she once again considers
how she wants her story to end.
How indecisive.
It feels perfectly in character
for this protagonist.
You may be right.
Okay, finish this draft to its end.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's wrap it up early.
You're going to the Suffragette's
reunion concert, right?
Yes.
Are you still undecided?
- Huh?
- About attending.
No. I'm going.
How could I not?
If you're so unsure,
why not stay here, with me?
- Huh?
- The exploration of love and sex.
It doesn't last forever, right?
Well...
You may fall out of love
with your husband one day, too.
So why not end it here,
and start a new journey, with me?
I...
Do you not want it to end?
I love you, Haru.
No, I don't.
Despite everything...
I love Ouji.
I'm sorry.
I knew that already.
Huh?
You're the only one who doesn't.
Thank you.
Enjoy the concert.
I will.
I always... always knew.
Why? Since when had I become so confused?
My feelings for him have never changed.
Not since the day we first met.
It's so easy. Ouji, I...
[Suffragette City - REBIRTH, 2026]
Aizawa?
Right, of course you'd come watch.
It's their reunion concert.
This is your first time attending a concert
as Ouji's wife, right?
Congrats.
Can we talk?
[Secrets]
We're almost up.
Is Haru coming?
Yeah. She never mentioned when, though.
Hope she makes it in time.
Yeah.
Please, explain. What is going on here?
Well...
What did Ouji say?
My husband said nothing.
Excuse me?
That good-for-nothing wimp.
I admit, I wanted to ruffle your feathers.
What?
But I only wanted to add a bit of spice.
Like a good curry.
Then, this was...
What do you think happened?
What would you do if he had cheated on you?
I wouldn't have done a thing.
Marriage doesn't make him my property.
I only wished to know the truth.
You've changed.
Of course we didn't do anything!
Not like we ever could.
- Huh?
- You already know, right?
I told him marriage wouldn't work
if he continued to hide his ED.
And just when I thought
we'd have a thrilling reunion,
he goes on and on
about his newlywed life and sex woes.
I don't know how to treat a girl
who used to be a fan.
But I can tell it's been rough on her.
Ouji went to you for advice...
About me?
He was seriously so annoying.
But I enjoyed the thrill
of not being a mother for once.
Can you blame me for being a little mean?
The concert is about to begin.
Thank you. We'll be right there.
♪ Embracing warm moments together ♪
♪ Your laugh is beautiful, yet sorrowful ♪
♪ The thoughtless words I spill ♪
♪ Make your tears bitter, yet sweet ♪
♪ Why is it I long for your profile? ♪
♪ Why is it I chase your fading shadow? ♪
♪ Why is it? Why can't I smile? ♪
♪ I always knew I was a lame guy ♪
♪ I had nothing to offer,
yet you stayed at my side ♪
♪ Because we called that happiness ♪
♪ A gift you bestowed to me ♪
♪ I love you, I love you so ♪
♪ I always knew I do ♪
Haru.
Weren't you in the middle of an after-party?
It's fine. I've raised a toast with the guys.
The party will last all night anyway.
So? How was the concert?
It was amazing.
I liked your new song, too. It felt sincere.
Seriously? Your compliment
means the most to me.
Huh?
You're an old, dedicated fan.
Of course I'd want to hear your thoughts.
I'm glad you liked it.
I'm a long-time fan.
You're always within arm's reach.
I'm allowed to monopolize your smiles.
My old self would be so jealous of me now.
Except...
Ouji.
I've changed. You've noticed, right?
Yeah. But I'm fine...
I know. I wasn't going to bring it up either.
Ouji.
I had sex with another man.
I have no right to be your wife.
[Preview]